
export const flags = {

  questions:[
    {
        key: 1,
        image: "AF" ,
        color: "linear-gradient(black,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[
        "Algeria",
           "Afghanistan",
           "Bangladesh",
           "Lebanon",],
          correct: "Afghanistan"
      },
      
      {
        key: 2,
        image: "AL",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red)",
        choices:[ "Malta",
           "Latvia",
           "Albania",
           "Cuba"],
          correct: "Albania"
      },
      {
        key: 3,
        image: "DZ",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red,white)",
        choices:[ "Algeria",
           "Pakistan",
           "Jordan",
           "Iran"],
          correct: "Algeria"
      },
      {
        key: 4,
        image: "AD",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,yellow,red)",
        choices:[ "Moldova",
           "Jamaica",
           "Andorra",
           "Estonia"],
          correct: "Andorra"
      },

      {
        key: 5,
        image: "AO",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red)",
        choices:[ "Nigeria",
           "Albania",
           "Benin",
           "Angola"],
          correct: "Angola"
      },

      {
        key: 6,
        image: "AG",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red)",
        choices:[ "Antigua and Barbuda",
           "Barbados",
           "Angola",
           "Cambodia"],
          correct: "Antigua and Barbuda"
      },

      {
        key: 7,
        image: "AR",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white)",
        choices:[ "Argentina",
           "Finland",
           "Paraguay",
           "Mexico"],
          correct: "Argentina"
      },

      {
        key: 8,
        image: "AM",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,blue,orange)",
        choices:[ "Denmark",
           "France",
           "Georgia",
           "Armenia"],
          correct: "Armenia"
      },

      {
        key: 9,
        image: "AU",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,red)",
        choices:[ "New Zealand",
           "Australia",
           "United kingdom",
           "Gibraltar"],
          correct: "Australia"
      },

      {
        key: 10,
        image: "AT",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        choices:[ "Austria",
           "Hungary",
           "Slovakia",
           "Poland"],
          correct: "Austria"
      },

      {
        key: 11,
        image: "AZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bosnia and Herzegovina",
           "Algeria",
           "Azerbaijan",
           "Turkey"],
          correct: "Azerbaijan"
      },

      {
        key: 12,
        image: "BS",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,black,yellow)",
        choices:[ "Barbados",
           "Brazil",
           "Bahrain",
           "Bahamas"],
          correct: "Bahamas"
      },

      {
        key: 13,
        image: "BH",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Qatar",
           "Bahrain",
           "Oman",
           "Iraq"],
          correct: "Bahrain"
      },

      {
        key: 14,
        image: "BD",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "India",
           "Laos",
           "Palau",
           "Bangladesh"],
          correct: "Bangladesh"
      },

      {
        key: 15,
        image: "BB",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,black,orange)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Barbados",
           "Fiji",
           "Bahamas",
           "Costa Rica"],
          correct: "Barbados"
      },

      {
        key: 16,
        image: "BY",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Russia",
           "Lithuania",
           "Latvia",
           "Belarus"],
          correct: "Belarus"
      },

      {
        key: 17,
        image: "BE",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Romania",
           "Belgium",
           "Germany",
           "Austria"],
          correct: "Belgium"
      },

      {
        key: 18,
        image: "BZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Costa Rica",
           "Jamaica",
           "Belize",
           "Haiti"],
          correct: "Belize"
      },

      {
        key: 19,
        image: "BJ",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Benin",
           "Ghana",
           "Chad",
           "South Africa"],
          correct: "Benin"
      },

      {
        key: 20,
        image: "BT",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,orange)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "China",
           "Japan",
           "North Korea",
           "Bhutan"],
          correct: "Bhutan"
      },

      {
        key: 21,
        image: "BO",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Peru",
           "Lithuania",
           "Bolivia",
           "Portugal"],
          correct: "Bolivia"
      },

      {
        key: 22,
        image: "BA",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Serbia",
           "Bosnia and Herzegovina",
           "Bulgaria",
           "North Macedonia"],
          correct: "Bosnia and Herzegovina"
      },

      {
        key: 23,
        image: "BW",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Kenya",
           "Gabon",
           "Burundi",
           "Botswana"],
          correct: "Botswana"
      },

      {
        key: 24,
        image: "BR",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Brazil",
           "Uruguay",
           "Belize",
           "Guatemala"],
          correct: "Brazil"
      },

      {
        key: 25,
        image: "BN",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Brunei",
           "Malaysia",
           "Laos",
           "Singapore"],
          correct: "Brunei"
      },

      {
        key: 26,
        image: "BG",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Russia",
           "Romania",
           "Bulgaria",
           "Slovenia"],
          correct: "Bulgaria"
      },

      {
        key: 27,
        image: "BF",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "South Africa",
           "Burundi",
           "Burkina Faso",
           "Cameroon"],
          correct: "Burkina Faso"
      },

      {
        key: 28,
        image: "BI",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Ghana",
           "Burundi",
           "Ethiopia",
           "Nigeria"],
          correct: "Burundi"
      },

      {
        key: 29,
        image: "KH",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bhutan",
           "China",
           "Malaysia",
           "Cambodia"],
          correct: "Cambodia"
      },

      {
        key: 30,
        image: "CM",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Cameroon",
           "Chad",
           "Togo",
           "Ivory Coast"],
          correct: "Cameroon"
      },

      {
        key: 31,
        image: "CA",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Lebanon",
           "Canada",
           "Cuba",
           "Malta"],
          correct: "Canada"
      },

      {
        key: 32,
        image: "CV",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Madagascar",
           "Mauritius",
           "Seychelles",
           "Cabo Verde"],
          correct: "Cabo Verde"
      },

      {
        key: 33,
        image: "CF",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,white,green,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Sierra Leone",
           "Botswana",
           "Mozambique",
           "Central African Republic"],
          correct: "Central African Republic"
      },

      {
        key: 34,
        image: "TD",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,orange,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Chad",
           "Ivory Coast",
           "Yemen",
           "Somalia"],
          correct: "Chad"
      },

      {
        key: 35,
        image: "CL",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Panama",
           "Chile",
           "Dominican Republic",
           "Ecuador"],
          correct: "Chile"
      },

      {
        key: 36,
        image: "CN",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "North Korea",
           "Japan",
           "China",
           "Malaysia"],
          correct: "China"
      },

      {
        key: 37,
        image: "CO",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,darkblue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Venezuela",
           "Ecuador",
           "Colombia",
           "Bolivia"],
          correct: "Colombia"
      },

      {
        key: 38,
        image: "KM",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,white,red,blue,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Comoros",
           "Azerbaijan",
           "Tunisia",
           "Turkey"],
          correct: "Comoros"
      },

      {
        key: 39,
        image: "CD",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Comoros",
           "South Africa",
           "Republic of Congo",
           "D. R. of Congo"],
          correct: "D. R. of Congo"
      },

      {
        key: 40,
        image: "CG",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Guyana",
           "South Africa",
           "Republic of Congo",
           "D. R. Congo"],
          correct: "Republic of Congo"
      },

      {
        key: 41,
        image: "CR",
        color: "linear-gradient(darkblue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Costa Rica",
           "Belize",
           "El Salvador",
           "Suriname"],
          correct: "Costa Rica"
      },

      {
        key: 42,
        image: "CI",
        color: "linear-gradient(orange,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Senegal",
           "Nigeria",
           "Ghana",
           "Ivory Coast"],
          correct: "Ivory Coast"
      },

      {
        key: 43,
        image: "HR",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Serbia",
           "Croatia",
           "Slovakia",
           "Slovenia"],
          correct: "Croatia"
      },

      {
        key: 44,
        image: "CU",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "St Lucia",
           "Cuba",
           "Barbados",
           "Haiti"],
          correct: "Cuba"
      },

      {
        key: 45,
        image: "CY",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,orange)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Cyprus",
           "Greece",
           "North Macedonia",
           "Malta"],
          correct: "Cyprus"
      },

      {
        key: 46,
        image: "CZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Czechia",
           "Croatia",
           "France",
           "Netherlands"],
          correct: "Czechia"
      },

      {
        key: 47,
        image: "DK",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Sweden",
           "Norway",
           "Finland",
           "Denmark"],
          correct: "Denmark"
      },

      {
        key: 48,
        image: "DJ",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,green,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Ethiopia",
           "Kenya",
           "Djibouti",
           "Somalia"],
          correct: "Djibouti"
      },

      {
        key: 49,
        image: "DM",
        color: "linear-gradient(green, red, yellow , white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Honduras",
           "Cuba",
           "Dominican Republic",
           "Dominica"],
          correct: "Dominica"
      },

      {
        key: 50,
        image: "DO",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Costa Rica",
           "Haiti",
           "Dominican Republic",
           "Dominica"],
          correct: "Dominican Republic"
      },

      {
        key: 51,
        image: "TL",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Brunei",
           "East Timor",
           "Palau",
           "Laos"],
          correct: "East Timor"
      },

      {
        key: 52,
        image: "EC",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Argentina",
           "Colombia",
           "Venezuela",
           "Ecuador"],
          correct: "Ecuador"
      },

      {
        key: 53,
        image: "EG",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Jordan",
           "Iraq",
           "Yemen",
           "Egypt"],
          correct: "Egypt"
      },

      {
        key: 54,
        image: "SV",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Mexico",
           "El Salvador",
           "Guatemala",
           "Honduras"],
          correct: "El Salvador"
      },

      {
        key: 55,
        image: "GQ",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Guinea",
           "Equatorial Guinea",
           "Chad",
           "Togo"],
          correct: "Equatorial Guinea"
      },

      {
        key: 56,
        image: "ER",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Eritrea",
           "Ethiopia",
           "Djibouti",
           "Comoros"],
          correct: "Eritrea"
      },

      {
        key: 57,
        image: "EE",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Belarus",
           "Poland",
           "Estonia",
           "Latvia"],
          correct: "Estonia"
      },

      {
        key: 58,
        image: "ET",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Ghana",
           "Kenya",
           "Somalia",
           "Ethiopia"],
          correct: "Ethiopia"
      },

      {
        key: 59,
        image: "FJ",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "New Zealand",
           "Fiji",
           "Samoa",
           "Tonga"],
          correct: "Fiji"
      },

      {
        key: 60,
        image: "FI",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Estonia",
           "Norway",
           "Denmark",
           "Finland"],
          correct: "Finland"
      },

      {
        key: 61,
        image: "FR",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Russia",
           "Canada",
           "France",
           "United Kingdom"],
          correct: "France"
      },

      {
        key: 62,
        image: "GA",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Uganda",
           "Kiribati",
           "Gabon",
           "India"],
          correct: "Gabon"
      },

      {
        key: 63,
        image: "GM",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Georgia",
           "Guinea",
           "Gabon",
           "Gambia"],
          correct: "Gambia"
      },

      {
        key: 64,
        image: "GE",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Georgia",
           "Armenia",
           "Iran",
           "Oman"],
          correct: "Georgia"
      },

      {
        key: 65,
        image: "DE",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Germany",
           "Austria",
           "Mauritania",
           "Romania"],
          correct: "Germany"
      },

      {
        key: 66,
        image: "GH",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Burkina Faso",
           "Ghana",
           "Senegal",
           "Cuba"],
          correct: "Ghana"
      },

      {
        key: 67,
        image: "GR",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Georgia",
           "Greece",
           "Finland",
           "Sweden"],
          correct: "Greece"
      },

      {
        key: 68,
        image: "GD",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Grenada",
           "Haiti",
           "Guyana",
           "Dominica"],
          correct: "Grenada"
      },

      {
        key: 69,
        image: "GT",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Togo",
           "Rwanda",
           "Guatemala",
           "El Salvador"],
          correct: "Guatemala"
      },

      {
        key: 70,
        image: "GW",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Liberia",
           "Guinea",
           "Senegal",
           "Guinea-Bissau"],
          correct: "Guinea-Bissau"
      },

      {
        key: 71,
        image: "GY",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Mali",
           "Guinea",
           "Guyana",
           "Malawi"],
          correct: "Guyana"
      },

      {
        key: 72,
        image: "HT",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Haiti",
           "Dominican Republic",
           "Panama",
           "San Marino"],
          correct: "Haiti"
      },

      {
        key: 73,
        image: "HN",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Haiti",
           "El Salvador",
           "Nicaragua",
           "Honduras"],
          correct: "Honduras"
      },

      {
        key: 74,
        image: "HU",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bulgaria",
           "Tajikistan",
           "Hungary",
           "Italy"],
          correct: "Hungary"
      },

      {
        key: 75,
        image: "IS",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Sweden",
           "Norway",
           "Denmark",
           "Iceland"],
          correct: "Iceland"
      },

      {
        key: 76,
        image: "IN",
        color: "linear-gradient(orange,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Nepal",
           "Sri Lanka",
           "Ireland",
           "India"],
          correct: "India"
      },

      {
        key: 77,
        image: "ID",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Indonesia",
           "Latvia",
           "Poland",
           "Cambodia"],
          correct: "Indonesia"
      },

      {
        key: 78,
        image: "IR",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Iran",
           "India",
           "Tajikistan",
           "Pakistan"],
          correct: "Iran"
      },

      {
        key: 79,
        image: "IQ",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Yemen",
           "Iraq",
           "Syria",
           "Kuwait"],
          correct: "Iraq"
      },

      {
        key: 80,
        image: "IE",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,orange)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Ireland",
           "Romania",
           "Mali",
           "Niger"],
          correct: "Ireland"
      },

      {
        key: 81,
        image: "IL",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Georgia",
           "Israel",
           "Greece",
           "Armenia"],
          correct: "Israel"
      },

      {
        key: 82,
        image: "IT",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Hungary",
           "Bulgaria",
           "Italy",
           "France"],
          correct: "Italy"
      },

      {
        key: 83,
        image: "JM",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Jamaica",
           "South Africa",
           "Mozambique",
           "Guyana"],
          correct: "Jamaica"
      },

      {
        key: 84,
        image: "JP",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "South Korea",
           "North Korea",
           "Japan",
           "Bangladesh"],
          correct: "Japan"
      },

      {
        key: 85,
        image: "JO",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,black,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Kuwait",
           "Oman",
           "Jordan",
           "UAE"],
          correct: "Jordan"
      },

      {
        key: 86,
        image: "KZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,yellow,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Micronesia",
           "Kazakhstan",
           "Rwanda",
           "Cabo Verde"],
          correct: "Kazakhstan"
      },

      {
        key: 87,
        image: "KE",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Comoros",
           "Sri Lanka",
           "South Sudan",
           "Kenya"],
          correct: "Kenya"
      },

      {
        key: 88,
        image: "KI",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Comoros",
           "Sri Lanka",
           "East Timor",
           "Kiribati"],
          correct: "Kiribati"
      },

      {
        key: 89,
        image: "KW",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,green,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Jordan",
           "UAE",
           "Kuwait",
           "Iran"],
          correct: "Kuwait"
      },

      {
        key: 90,
        image: "KG",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Uzbekistan",
           "Georgia",
           "North Macedonia",
           "Kyrgyzstan"],
          correct: "Kyrgyzstan"
      },

      {
        key: 91,
        image: "LA",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Laos",
           "Palau",
           "Cambodia",
           "Micronesia"],
          correct: "Laos"
      },

      {
        key: 92,
        image: "LV",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Lithuania",
           "Slovakia",
           "Latvia",
           "Slovenia"],
          correct: "Latvia"
      },

      {
        key: 93,
        image: "LB",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Wales",
           "Canada",
           "Peru",
           "Lebanon"],
          correct: "Lebanon"
      },

      {
        key: 94,
        image: "LS",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Sierra Leone",
           "Lesotho",
           "Suriname",
           "Malawi"],
          correct: "Lesotho"
      },

      {
        key: 95,
        image: "LR",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Liberia",
           "USA",
           "Costa Rica",
           "Haiti"],
          correct: "Liberia"
      },

      {
        key: 96,
        image: "LY",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,black,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Tunisia",
           "Pakistan",
           "Libya",
           "Azerbaijan"],
          correct: "Libya"
      },

      {
        key: 97,
        image: "LI",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Andorra",
           "Luxembourg",
           "San Marino",
           "Liechtenstein"],
          correct: "Liechtenstein"
      },

      {
        key: 98,
        image: "LT",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Romania",
           "Lithuania",
           "Moldova",
           "Latvia"],
          correct: "Lithuania"
      },

      {
        key: 99,
        image: "LU",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,lighblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Netherlands",
           "Serbia",
           "Luxembourg",
           "Slovenia"],
          correct: "Luxembourg"
      },

      {
        key: 100,
        image: "MG",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Rwanda",
           "Benin",
           "Malawi",
           "Madagascar"],
          correct: "Madagascar"
      },

      {
        key: 101,
        image: "MW",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Rwanda",
           "Sierra Leone",
           "Madagascar",
           "Malawi"],
          correct: "Malawi"
      },

      {
        key: 102,
        image: "MY",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,white,red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Kiribati",
           "Indonesia",
           "Singapore",
           "Malaysia"],
          correct: "Malaysia"
      },

      {
        key: 103,
        image: "MV",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Tunisia",
           "Pakistan",
           "Maldives",
           "Azerbaijan"],
          correct: "Maldives"
      },

      {
        key: 104,
        image: "ML",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Cameroon",
           "Guinea",
           "Benin",
           "Mali"],
          correct: "Mali"
      },

      {
        key: 105,
        image: "MT",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Andorra",
           "Liechtenstein",
           "Monaco",
           "Malta"],
          correct: "Malta"
      },

      {
        key: 106,
        image: "MH",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Marshall Islands",
           "Cabo Verde",
           "Micronesia",
           "Nauru"],
          correct: "Marshall Islands"
      },

      {
        key: 107,
        image: "MR",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Comoros",
           "Maldives",
           "Mauritania",
           "Pakistan"],
          correct: "Mauritania"
      },

      {
        key: 108,
        image: "MU",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,blue,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Maldives",
           "Mauritius",
           "Seychelles",
           "Cabo Verde"],
          correct: "Mauritius"
      },

      {
        key: 109,
        image: "MX",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Guatemala",
           "Peru",
           "Bolivia",
           "Mexico"],
          correct: "Mexico"
      },

      {
        key: 110,
        image: "FM",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Micronesia",
           "Somalia",
           "Palau",
           "Saint Lucia"],
          correct: "Micronesia"
      },

      {
        key: 111,
        image: "MD",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Andorra",
           "Romania",
           "Moldova",
           "Lithuania"],
          correct: "Moldova"
      },

      {
        key: 112,
        image: "MC",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Luxembourg",
           "Poland",
           "Malta",
           "Monaco"],
          correct: "Monaco"
      },

      {
        key: 113,
        image: "MG",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bangladesh",
           "Sri Lanka",
           "Nepal",
           "Mongolia"],
          correct: "Mongolia"
      },

      {
        key: 114,
        image: "ME",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bosnia & Herzegovina",
           "Albania",
           "Montenegro",
           "Kyrgyzstan"],
          correct: "Montenegro"
      },

      {
        key: 115,
        image: "MA",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Egypt",
           "Albania",
           "Morocco",
           "Montenegro"],
          correct: "Morocco"
      },

      {
        key: 116,
        image: "MZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,black,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Rwanda",
           "Namibia",
           "Mozambique",
           "Angola"],
          correct: "Mozambique"
      },

      {
        key: 117,
        image: "MM",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Malaysia",
           "Vietnam",
           "Thailand",
           "Myanmar"],
          correct: "Myanmar"
      },

      {
        key: 118,
        image: "NA",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Malawi",
           "South Africa",
           "Namibia",
           "Rwanda"],
          correct: "Namibia"
      },

      {
        key: 119,
        image: "NR",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Nicaragua",
           "Cabo Verde",
           "Marshall Islands",
           "Nauru"],
          correct: "Nauru"
      },

      {
        key: 120,
        image: "NP",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Turkmenistan",
           "Sri Lanka",
           "Nepal",
           "Mongolia"],
          correct: "Nepal"
      },

      {
        key: 121,
        image: "NL",
        color: "linear-gradient(red, white, blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Netherlands",
           "Luxembourg",
           "Russia",
           "Slovakia"],
          correct: "Netherlands"
      },

      {
        key: 122,
        image: "NZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Australia",
           "United Kingdom",
           "New Zealand",
           "Fiji"],
          correct: "New Zealand"
      },

      {
        key: 123,
        image: "NI",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Guatemala",
           "El Salvador",
           "Honduras",
           "Nicaragua"],
          correct: "Nicaragua"
      },

      {
        key: 124,
        image: "NE",
        color: "linear-gradient(orange,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Sri Lanka",
           "Rwanda",
           "Niger",
           "India"],
          correct: "Niger"
      },

      {
        key: 125,
        image: "NG",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Namibia",
           "South Africa",
           "Sierra Leone",
           "Nigeria"],
          correct: "Nigeria"
      },

      {
        key: 126,
        image: "KP",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "North Korea",
           "Laos",
           "South Korea",
           "Singapore"],
          correct: "North Korea"
      },

      {
        key: 127,
        image: "MK",
        color: "linear-gradient(red, yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "North Macedonia",
           "Uganda",
           "Zambia",
           "Niger"],
          correct: "North Macedonia"
      },

      {
        key: 128,
        image: "NO",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Iceland",
           "Denmark",
           "Norway",
           "Sweden"],
          correct: "Norway"
      },

      {
        key: 129,
        image: "OM",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Oman",
           "Tajikistan",
           "Uzbekistan",
           "Turkmenistan"],
          correct: "Oman"
      },

      {
        key: 130,
        image: "PK",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Maldives",
           "Tunisia",
           "Libya",
           "Turkmenistan"],
          correct: "Pakistan"
      },

      {
        key: 131,
        image: "PW",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,yellow,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Micronesia",
           "Palau",
           "North Korea",
           "Nauru"],
          correct: "Palau"
      },

      {
        key: 132,
        image: "PA",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Chile",
           "Guatemala",
           "Panama",
           "Uruguay"],
          correct: "Panama"
      },

      {
        key: 133,
        image: "PG",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Madagascar",
           "Papua New Guinea",
           "Panama",
           "Solomon Islands"],
          correct: "Papua New Guinea"
      },

      {
        key: 134,
        image: "PY",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Peru",
           "Panama",
           "Paraguay",
           "Uruguay"],
          correct: "Paraguay"
      },

      {
        key: 135,
        image: "PE",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Peru",
           "Canada",
           "Belgium",
           "Samoa"],
          correct: "Peru"
      },

      {
        key: 136,
        image: "PH",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue, white, red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Togo",
           "Tonga",
           "Namibia",
           "Philippines"],
          correct: "Philippines"
      },

      {
        key: 137,
        image: "PL",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Monaco",
           "Poland",
           "Indonesia",
           "Malta"],
          correct: "Poland"
      },

      {
        key: 138,
        image: "PT",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Mozambique",
           "Rwanda",
           "Portugal",
           "South Africa"],
          correct: "Portugal"
      },

      {
        key: 139,
        image: "QA",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,darkred)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bahrain",
           "Tunisia",
           "Yemen",
           "Qatar"],
          correct: "Qatar"
      },

      {
        key: 140,
        image: "RO",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "North Macedonia",
           "Niger",
           "Togo",
           "Romania"],
          correct: "Romania"
      },

      {
        key: 141,
        image: "RU",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Slovenia",
           "Russia",
           "Netherlands",
           "Ukraine"],
          correct: "Russia"
      },

      {
        key: 142,
        image: "RW",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Zambia",
           "Tajikistan",
           "Uzbekistan",
           "Rwanda"],
          correct: "Rwanda"
      },

      {
        key: 143,
        image: "KN",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,black,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Solomon Islands",
           "Tuvalu",
           "Saint Lucia",
           "Saint Kitts & Nevis"],
          correct: "Saint Kitts & Nevis"
      },

      {
        key: 144,
        image: "LC",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,yellow,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Somalia",
           "Palau",
           "Saint Lucia",
           "Saint Kitts & Nevis"],
          correct: "Saint Lucia"
      },

      {
        key: 145,
        image: "WS",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Solomon Islands",
           "Samoa",
           "Fiji",
           "Tonga"],
          correct: "Samoa"
      },

      {
        key: 146,
        image: "SM",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Micronesia",
           "Saint Lucia",
           "San Marino",
           "Estonia"],
          correct: "San Marino"
      },

      {
        key: 147,
        image: "ST",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Micronesia",
           "Sao Tome & Principe",
           "Tuvalu",
           "Saint Kitts & Nevis"],
          correct: "Sao Tome & Principe"
      },

      {
        key: 148,
        image: "SA",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Jordan",
           "UAE",
           "Saudi Arabia",
           "Libya"],
          correct: "Saudi Arabia"
      },

      {
        key: 149,
        image: "SN",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Somalia",
           "Senegal",
           "Ghana",
           "Cameroon"],
          correct: "Senegal"
      },

      {
        key: 150,
        image: "RS",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Croatia",
           "Slovenia",
           "Serbia",
           "Slovakia"],
          correct: "Serbia"
      },

      {
        key: 151,
        image: "SC",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow,red,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Seychelles",
           "Mauritius",
           "Madagascar",
           "Cabo Verde"],
          correct: "Seychelles"
      },

      {
        key: 152,
        image: "SL",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Gabon",
           "Togo",
           "Sierra Leone",
           "Rwanda"],
          correct: "Sierra Leone"
      },

      {
        key: 153,
        image: "SG",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Singapore",
           "Malaysia",
           "Indonesia",
           "East Timor"],
          correct: "Singapore"
      },

      {
        key: 154,
        image: "SK",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Netherlands",
           "Czechia",
           "Slovakia",
           "Slovenia"],
          correct: "Slovakia"
      },

      {
        key: 155,
        image: "SI",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Serbia",
           "Russia",
           "Slovakia",
           "Slovenia"],
          correct: "Slovenia"
      },

      {
        key: 156,
        image: "SB",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Tanzania",
           "Maldives",
           "Tuvalu",
           "Solomon Islands"],
          correct: "Solomon Islands"
      },

      {
        key: 157,
        image: "SO",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Somalia",
           "San Marino",
           "Israel",
           "Lesotho"],
          correct: "Somalia"
      },

      {
        key: 158,
        image: "ZA",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,green,red,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Mozambique",
           "Zimbabwe",
           "Zambia",
           "South Africa"],
          correct: "South Africa"
      },

      {
        key: 159,
        image: "KR",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red,blue,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Thailand",
           "Japan",
           "South Korea",
           "North Korea"],
          correct: "South Korea"
      },

      {
        key: 160,
        image: "SS",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,black,red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Togo",
           "Mozambique",
           "Sudan",
           "South Sudan"],
          correct: "South Sudan"
      },

      {
        key: 161,
        image: "ES",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Malta",
           "Andorra",
           "Spain",
           "Portugal"],
          correct: "Spain"
      },

      {
        key: 162,
        image: "LK",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,red,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Lebanon",
           "Zambia",
           "Tuvalu",
           "Sri Lanka"],
          correct: "Sri Lanka"
      },

      {
        key: 163,
        image: "SD",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red,white,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Kuwait",
           "Jordan",
           "UAE",
           "Sudan"],
          correct: "Sudan"
      },

      {
        key: 164,
        image: "SR",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white,red,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Burkina Faso",
           "Guyana",
           "Burundi",
           "Suriname"],
          correct: "Suriname"
      },

      {
        key: 165,
        image: "SE",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Norway",
           "Sweden",
           "Finland",
           "Iceland"],
          correct: "Sweden"
      },

      {
        key: 166,
        image: "CH",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Poland",
           "Malta",
           "England",
           "Switzerland"],
          correct: "Switzerland"
      },

      {
        key: 167,
        image: "SY",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Kuwait",
           "Yemen",
           "Syria",
           "Iraq"],
          correct: "Syria"
      },

      {
        key: 168,
        image: "TW",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Taiwan",
           "China",
           "North Korea",
           "South Korea"],
          correct: "Taiwan"
      },

      {
        key: 169,
        image: "TJ",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Uzbekistan",
           "Kazakhstan",
           "Tajikistan",
           "Turkmenistan"],
          correct: "Tajikistan"
      },

      {
        key: 170,
        image: "TZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,black,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Malawi",
           "Zambia",
           "Tanzania",
           "Namibia"],
          correct: "Tanzania"
      },

      {
        key: 171,
        image: "TH",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,blue,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Laos",
           "Thailand",
           "Vietnam",
           "Cambodia"],
          correct: "Thailand"
      },

      {
        key: 172,
        image: "TG",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,yellow,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Tanzania",
           "Senegal",
           "Togo",
           "Benin"],
          correct: "Togo"
      },

      {
        key: 173,
        image: "TO",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Malta",
           "Tonga",
           "Switzerland",
           "Samoa"],
          correct: "Tonga"
      },

      {
        key: 174,
        image: "TT",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,black,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Trinidad & Tobago",
           "Tonga",
           "Switzerland",
           "Samoa"],
          correct: "Trinidad & Tobago"
      },

      {
        key: 175,
        image: "TN",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Algeria",
           "Morocco",
           "Turkey",
           "Tunisia"],
          correct: "Tunisia"
      },

      {
        key: 176,
        image: "TR",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,white,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Algeria",
           "Azerbaijan",
           "Turkey",
           "Tunisia"],
          correct: "Turkey"
      },

      {
        key: 177,
        image: "TM",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Maldives",
           "Tajikistan",
           "Turkmenistan",
           "Algeria"],
          correct: "Turkmenistan"
      },

      {
        key: 178,
        image: "TV",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white,lightblue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Maldives",
           "Tuvalu",
           "New Zealand",
           "Fiji"],
          correct: "Tuvalu"
      },

      {
        key: 179,
        image: "UG",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Papua New Guinea",
           "Togo",
           "Tanzania",
           "Uganda"],
          correct: "Uganda"
      },

      {
        key: 180,
        image: "UA",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Ukraine",
           "Poland",
           "Russia",
           "Latvia"],
          correct: "Ukraine"
      },

      {
        key: 181,
        image: "AE",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,green,white,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Jordan",
           "Iraq",
           "UAE",
           "Kuwait"],
          correct: "UAE"
      },

      {
        key: 182,
        image: "GB",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Fiji",
           "New Zealand",
           "Australia",
           "United Kingdom"],
          correct: "United Kingdom"
      },

      {
        key: 183,
        image: "US",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Russia",
           "China",
           "USA",
           "Liberia"],
          correct: "USA"
      },

      {
        key: 184,
        image: "UY",
        color: "linear-gradient(white,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Uruguay",
           "Paraguay",
           "Argentina",
           "Ecuador"],
          correct: "Uruguay"
      },

      {
        key: 185,
        image: "UZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(lightblue,white,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Uruguay",
           "Paraguay",
           "Uzbekistan",
           "Tajikistan"],
          correct: "Uzbekistan"
      },

      {
        key: 186,
        image: "VU",
        color: "linear-gradient(black,red,green)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Tanzania",
           "Tuvalu",
           "Eritrea",
           "Vanuatu"],
          correct: "Vanuatu"
      },

      {
        key: 187,
        image: "VA",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,white)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Andorra",
           "San Marino",
           "Vatican City",
           "Malta"],
          correct: "Vatican City"
      },

      {
        key: 188,
        image: "VE",
        color: "linear-gradient(yellow,blue,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Bolivia",
           "Venezuela",
           "Ecuador",
           "Colombia"],
          correct: "Venezuela"
      },

      {
        key: 189,
        image: "VN",
        color: "linear-gradient(red,yellow,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Vietnam",
           "China",
           "Thailand",
           "Malaysia"],
          correct: "Vietnam"
      },

      {
        key: 190,
        image: "YE",
        color: "linear-gradient(red, white, black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Kuwait",
           "Iraq",
           "Syria",
           "Yemen"],
          correct: "Yemen"
      },

      {
        key: 191,
        image: "ZM",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,red)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Benin",
           "Burundi",
           "Namibia",
           "Zambia"],
          correct: "Zambia"
      },

      {
        key: 191,
        image: "ZW",
        color: "linear-gradient(green,yellow,red,black)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Zimbabwe",
           "Burundi",
           "Tanzania",
           "Zambia"],
          correct: "Zimbabwe"
      },

      {
        key: 192,
        image: "AW",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,red,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Dominica",
           "Micronesia",
           "Aruba",
           "Palau"],
          correct: "Aruba"
      },

      {
        key: 193,
        image: "SZ",
        color: "linear-gradient(blue,yellow,red,yellow,blue)",
        question:  "Q. What country is this the flag of?",
        choices:[ "Tanzania",
           "South Africa",
           "Lesotho",
           "Eswatini"],
          correct: "Eswatini"
      },
]


}

export const resultInitialState = {
  score: 0,
  correctAnswers: 0,
  wrongAnswers: 0,
}

